{"data":[{"question":"Manager Churchill gave up drinking for a while, but soon ___ to his old ways.","a":"returns","b":"returned","c":"had returned","d":"was returning","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the Simple Past to list a series of completed actions in the past: gave up- returned","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"You're smoking too much. \"Only at home. No one ___ me but you.\"","a":"had seen","b":"is seeing","c":"saw","d":"sees","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual. The action can be a habit, a hobby, a daily event, a scheduled event or something that often happens. \n+ Smoking is a habit-> simple present tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Selecting a mobile phone or a computer for personal use is no easy task because technology ___ so rapidly.","a":"has changed","b":"is changing","c":"will change","d":"will have changed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use the Present Continuous with normal verbs to express the idea that something is happening now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Peggy ___ table tennis quite well, but she hasn't had time to play since the Chinese New Year.","a":"have played","b":"will play","c":"plays","d":"played","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual. The action can be a habit, a hobby, a daily event, a scheduled event or something that often happens","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Visitors ___ not to photograph the animals.","a":"are requested","b":"will request","c":"request","d":"are requesting","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: (Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual. The action can be a habit, a hobby, a daily event, a scheduled event or something that often happens) + Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Not only I but also my classmates ___ tired of having one examination after another.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"be","d":"am","answer":"1","explain":"\n- If you use either-or\/ neither-nor\/not only- but also: look at the subject closest to the verb. If the subject closest to the verb is singular, use a singular verb; likewise, if the subject is plural, use a plural verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"A library with one hundred thousand books ___ to the country as a gift.","a":"has offered","b":"is offered","c":"have offered","d":"are offered","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When using as well as, except, in addition to, no less than, and with, the noun before these phrases determines the number","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"When, where and how to build the new stadium ___ yet.","a":"are not decided","b":"is not decided","c":"have not decided","d":"has not decided","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Have no information about the stadium. It is true - present simple \n- Stadium can't build it self - passive tense.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The number of guests invited ___ thirty, but a number of them ___ absent for different reason.","a":"was, was","b":"were, was","c":"were, were","d":"was, were","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The expression the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"All the preparations for the contest ___, and we're ready to start.","a":"complete","b":"completed","c":"have been completed","d":"had been completed","answer":"3","explain":"- The passive voice in present perfect","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}